这个混蛋是个警察
This bastard is a cop.
他知道我们通过这艘船运毒品
He knew we were bringing drugs through this boat.
好好照顾他
Take care of him.
嘿，把他用塑料袋包起来挂起来
Hey, wrap him up in plastic and hang him up.
嘿
Hey.
你不能杀他
You can't kill him.
为什么? 我不能杀警察吗？
Why? Can't I kill the police?
你怎么找到这个地方的？
How did you find this place?
我觉得他在追我
I think he's after me.
你这个混蛋！
You bastard!
你做了什么把警察带来了？
What did you do to bring the police?
你..
You...
我告诉过你要小心
I told you to be careful.
好了，别说了
Okay, so stop.
住手！
Stop it!
我要走了
I'm going.
这个月我投了更多的钱
I put in more money this month.
那毒品呢？
What about the drugs?
我赚了20公斤，马上就好
I'm making 20 kilos. I'll be ready soon.
但你必须悄悄行动
But you have to move quietly.
我对日本的毒品交易持怀疑态度
I'm suspicious of the drug sales in Japan.
为明天的生物会议做好准备
Get ready for the bio meeting tomorrow.
你先置我于危险之中！
You put me in danger first!
过来！
Come here!
你要去哪里？
Where are you going?
你有危险吗？
Are you in danger?
把摄像机放下！
Put the camera down!
我从早上开始就要揍你！
I'm going to hit you from the morning!
你怎么了？
What's wrong with you?
别打我！
Don't hit me!
你在看什么？
What are you looking at?
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
你打人了？
You hit a person?
是的，长官
Yes, sir.
请进
Come in.
进去吧
Go in.
进去！
Go in!
嘿，站住！
Hey, stop!
你怎么了？
What's wrong with you?
你到底是什么？
What are you?
这是肇事逃逸吗？
Is this a hit and run?
走吧
Just go.
在我杀了你之前
Before I kill you.
我在问你
I'm asking you.
别问我
Don't ask me.
什么？
What?
我会把你所有的纹身都擦掉
I'll erase all your tattoos.
别来，别来
Don't come, don't come.
我真的要捅死你
I'm really going to stab you.
我要捅死你
I'm going to stab you.
太危险了
It's dangerous.
你知道的
You know.
警察，警察
Police, police.
你得快点过来
You have to come quickly.
我先来
I'll start.
这里，这里，还有这里
Here, here and here.
有人受伤了
There's someone who's hurt.
你吓到我了
You scared me.
不，不是我
No, it's not me.
不是我
It's not me.
别动
Stay still.
不，不是我
No, it's not me.
我是广州大学的教职员
I'm a staff member of Gwangsu University.
告诉他们你没看见我
Tell them you didn't see me.
对不起，但是请尽快把车开走
I'm sorry, but please get the car out of here quickly.
我得去上班了
I have to go to work.
很晚了，很晚了
It's late, it's late.
你之前抓到的那些混蛋很坏
Hey, the bastards you caught earlier are being bad.
Seocho-dong 刀案
Seocho-dong knife crime case.
我有一年没抓到你了，但你是怎么抓到的？
I haven't caught you for a year, but how did you catch it?
你看看就知道了
You can tell by looking at it.
嘿，Seok-do
Hey, Seok-do.
警察正在证明这是真的
The police are proving it as a real thing.
所以我才带你来
That's why I brought you.
嘿，但请给我一个好的方式
Hey, but please bring me in a good way.
我可没那么容易
Oh, I'm not that easy.
我没那么容易
I'm not that easy.
警察是什么？
What's a police?
不是很多人吗？
Isn't it a crowd of people?
你怎么能把拐杖弄得人山人海？
How do you make a cane a crowd?
但是 Seok-do 来了之后，他的表现有所提高
But after Seok-do came, his performance improved.
别说了
Stop it.
我只能在镜子里看到你的鼻子
I can only see your nose in the mirror.
你20岁的时候，放弃了拳击，开始当警察
When you were 20, you quit boxing and started to police.
我找到的时候就感觉到了
I felt it when I found it.
嘿，吃一个这个
Hey, have one of these.
我给你个球
I'll give you a ball.
我妻子给我的
My wife gave it to me.
给我
Give it to me.
我不会给你的
I don't give it to you.
这是用 A 级钢做的
This is made of grade A steel.
谢谢你的晚餐
Thank you for the meal.
对恢复能量很有好处
It's very good for the recovery of energy.
我要留著这个昂贵的一个半
I'm saving this expensive one and half.
如果你救了它，你会崩溃的
If you save it, you'll collapse.
全部吃掉
Eat it all.
真是浪费
It's a waste.
你吃吗？
Do you eat one?
我吃了一半怎么会有好的效果？
How can I have a good effect when I eat half?
我喜欢这个
Um, I like this.
很好
Good.
这是什么？
What's this?
你好
Hello.
这些都在哪儿？
Where's all this?
是的，你好
Yes, hello.
你吃了多少？
How many did you eat?
你知道这有多贵吗？
Do you know how expensive this is?
我知道什么？
What do I know?
你要这样对我吗？
Are you doing this to me?
是的，没错
Yes, that's right.
你们这些混蛋
You bastards.
是的，是的，是的
Yes, yes, yes.
是的，我明白了
Yes, I see.
办公室里有个案子
There's been a case in front of the office.
我得走了
I have to go.
手机
Cell phone.
在哪里？
Where is it?
这边请
This way
受害者是一名28岁的女性
The victim is a 28 year old woman
她从八楼摔下来
She fell from the 8th floor
那边没有闭路电视
There is no CCTV over there
所以我们无法确定死亡时间
So we can't confirm the time of death
我们在酒店里看到了闭路电视
We saw a CCTV inside the hotel
有一个人和两个人
There was a man and two people
但他离开的时候是一个人
But the man was alone when he left
但是他的脸没有被捕捉到
But his face was not captured
这边请
This way
我已经联系了死者家属
I've contacted the family of the deceased.
嘿，你来了
Hey, you're here.
我觉得没有其他证据了
I don't think there's any other evidence
除了在房间里喝酒
other than the drinking in the room.
有个关于男人的问题
There's a question about a man.
这不是同义词
It's not a synonymous.
为什么不是同义词? 他是外国人吗？
Why is it not a synonymous? Is he a foreigner?
我让他们调查一下
I told them to look into it.
闭路电视正在追踪受害者的行踪
The victim's whereabouts are being traced by the CCTV.
看看有没有目击者
Let's see if there's a witness.
好吧
Okay.
受害者去了一家俱乐部
The victim went to a club.
手环上写著呢
It was written on the wristband.
橘子俱乐部？
Club Orange?
我们先复印一份
Let's get a copy first.
好吧
Okay.
这是酒店受害者 Go Sun-hee 的尸检报告
This is the autopsy report of the hotel's fallen victim, Go Sun-hee.
外伤是颅骨骨折和颅骨破裂
The trauma is a skull fracture and a broken skull.
这是在倒下的尸体中常见的症状
It's a common symptom found in fallen bodies.
直接原因是心脏骤停
The direct cause is cardiac arrest.
病因是血液中的药物
The cause is a drug from the blood.
这是..
This is...
等等，毒品？
Wait, a drug?
是的
Yes.
这是一种新药，叫兴奋剂
It's a new drug called Hyper.
它比可卡因和氟哌啶强多了
It's much stronger than cocaine or filopon.
毒性和海洛因一样，所以非常危险
It's as toxic as heroin, so it's very dangerous.
在受害者的血液中发现了很多毒品
A lot of drugs have been detected in the victim's blood.
她死后有人扔的吗？
So someone threw it after she died?
是的
Yes.
她和受害者在一个俱乐部里
She was in a club with the victim.
她差点惹上麻烦
She almost got into trouble.
这之后再进去
Go in after this.
好吧
Okay.
嘿，Seok-do
Hey, Seok-do.
他说什么？
What did he say?
他说他喝了俱乐部的毒品后失去了理智
He said he lost his mind after drinking the drug from a club.
他说他再也没有见过 Go Sun-hee 了
He said he didn't see Go Sun-hee anymore.
他一定是喝了药，然后喝了
He must have drunk the drug and drank it.
我会把这个发给缉毒组
I'll send this to the drug squad.
我们把这个处理掉
Let's get rid of this.
这是谋杀案
This is a murder case.
真的吗？
Really?
我来吧，别发了
I'll do this. Don't send it.
我们得查查俱乐部的监控录像
We need to check the CCTV at the club.
他们不合作
They're not cooperating.
我已经发出了搜查令
I've already sent a search warrant.
谁是老大？
Who's the boss?
有三个老板
There are three bosses.
其中一个是李相哲，一个流氓
One of them is Lee Sang-chul, a gangster.
他一直不接电话
He hasn't been answering his phone.
我们走吧
Let's just go.
没有搜查令我们怎么去？
How can we go without a warrant?
我们可以走了
We can just go.
我们不能
We can't.
我们想不到夜总会
We can't think of the nightclub.
我们不能进去
We can't go in.
为什么不呢？
Why not?
水管理太差了
The water management is so bad.
因为你，我们不能进去
We can't go in because of you.
跟我来
Follow me.
就是这里，对吧？
This is the place, right?
是的，橙色
Yes, Orange.
我很久没去俱乐部了
It's been a while since I went to a club.
这家伙怎么还不来？
Why isn't this guy coming?
看看他，多帅啊
Look at him. He's so handsome.
嘿！
Hey!
他怎么了？
What's wrong with him?
他是黑社会吗？
Is he a gangster?
嘿，他们在看我们
Hey, they're looking at us.
我害怕，我害怕
I'm scared. I'm scared.
看他笑的
Look at him laughing.
为什么? 他为什么笑？
Why? Why is he laughing?
我要死了
I'm dying.
他和你一样是明星吗？
Is he a star like you?
也许吧
Well, maybe.
老板！
Boss!
快点
Hurry up.
这是 Ja Dong-moon
This is Ja Dong-moon.
江南区的生意就是他做的
He's the one who runs the Gangnam business.
很高兴见到你，东月
Nice to meet you, Dong-moon.
很高兴见到你，老板
Nice to meet you, boss.
我只需要让他进来
I just need to let him in.
但如果你是警探，我就有麻烦了
But if you're a detective, I'm in trouble.
安静
Be quiet.
我进去
I'll go in.
东月！
Dong-moon!
是的，兄弟
Yes, brother.
钱呢？
Where's the money?
他来了
He's here.
你的衣服怎么了？
What's wrong with your clothes?
你不是来拿钱的吧？
You're not here to get money, are you?
我是个警探
I'm a detective.
你可以进去了
You can go in.
谢谢你
Thank you.
不，我有个同事在这里，在 MVP 房间
No, I have a colleague here, in the MVP room.
走开
Go away.
别碰它，我这么说是因为我认识一个人
Don't touch it, I'm saying this because I know someone.
看看这个
Look at this.
走开
Go away.
你听不到我说话吗？
Can't you hear me?
把钱给我
Give me the money.
哦，该死
Oh, shit.
回头见
See you later.
后会有期
See you again.
嘿，谢谢
Hey, thanks.
你不是经常来吗？
Aren't you coming too often?
这种地方在哪里？
Hey, where is a place like this?
你们没有高吊舱吗？
Don't you have a high-pod?
质量不错，对吧？
The quality is good, right?
我今天要拍张好照片
I'll take a good picture today.
把你知道的都告诉我
Give me everything you have.
哦，兄弟
Oh, brother.
如果你吃得太多，这是..
If you feed too much, this is...
我有麻烦了
I'm in trouble.
我会处理的
Hey, I'll take care of it.
真漂亮
It's beautiful.
大家好
Hello, everyone.
二，四，六，七，八
Two, four, six, seven, eight.
搞什么？
What the fuck?
这是毒品，对吧？
This is drugs, right?
什么？
What?
你这个混蛋
You bastard.
你不接受吗？
You're not taking it?
这不是营养补充剂
It's not a nutritional supplement.
我不接受
I'm not taking it.
你这个混蛋
You bastard.
你他妈的混蛋，你不接受吗？
You fucking bastard. You're not taking it?
嘿，你是我爸爸的..
Hey, you're my dad's...
什么，怎么了？
What? What is it?
是的
Yeah.
拿著
Take it.
是毒品
It's drugs.
是毒品吗？
It's drugs?
是的
Yeah.
给总部打电话，把这个混蛋带走
Call headquarters and take this bastard.
从现在开始我要把它放在这里
I'm going to put it in here from now on.
我遇到了一些最近不怎么认识的朋友
I met some friends who are too hot to meet these days.
很高兴认识你
Nice to meet you.
我们走吧
Let's go.
是谁？
Who is it?
是的
Yeah.
是新来的守卫吗？
Is it a new guard?
你不能就这么闯进来，出去
Hey, you can't just come in like that. Get out.
嘿，嘿，嘿，等一下
Hey, hey, hey, wait a minute.
等一下，等一下
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
把这个，这个，还有这个放进去
Put this and this and this in here.
是的
Yeah.
到底是什么，到底是什么？
So what is it? What is it?
差不多吧
There's something like that.
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
效果不错
It came out well.
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
你为什么把这个放进去？
Why are you putting this in?
嘿，看这里
Hey, look here.
这是什么？
What is it?
你为什么把这个放进去？
Why are you putting this in?
好吧
Okay.
不，但是这个..
No, but this...
坐下，坐下
Sit down. Sit down.
你这个混蛋
You're a fucking bastard.
外面有人吗？
Hey, is there anyone out there?
操，真的
Fuck, really.
你在这里
You were here.
你他妈的..
You fucking...
嘿，不要
Hey, don't.
好痛
It hurts so much.
嘿
Hey.
哦，该死！
Oh, shit!
你是这里的工人，对吧？
You're a worker here, right?
对不起
I'm sorry.
老大呢？
Where's the boss?
我，我，我，我！
Me, me, me, me!
我没开玩笑！
I'm not kidding!
我，我，我，我！
Me, me, me, me!
我没开玩笑！
I'm not kidding!
我，我，我，我！
Me, me, me, me!
哦，该死！
Oh, shit!
等等，等等
Wait, wait, wait.
该死，是警卫吗？
Oh, shit! Is it a guard?
李相哲
Lee Sang-chul.
李相哲？
Lee Sang-chul?
你个狗娘养的！
You son of a bitch!
哦，该死！
Oh, shit!
你怎么了？
What's wrong with you?
怎么了? 你是黑社会吗？
What's wrong? Are you a gangster?
不，他是个流氓
No, he's a gangster.
你们这些混蛋
Oh, you bastards.
嘿，万子，干得好
Hey, Man-ja, good job.
是的
Yes.
你要上哪辆车？
Which car are you getting in?
这是什么？
What's this?
锡珠，干得好
Oh, Seok-joo, good job.
就这些吗？
Hey, is that all?
等一下
Wait a minute.
这只是个开始
It's just the beginning.
警察是真的
The police are real.
我们得把他们都抓起来
We need to catch them all.
你来了
You're here.
我在这里
I'm here.
你来了，兄弟
You're here, brother.
好久不见
Long time no see.
打个招呼
Say hello.
这位是白先生
This is Mr. Baek.
很高兴认识你
Nice to meet you.
求你了
Please.
我在朝鲜的客户都是赵先生的
My customers in North Korea are all from Mr. Jo.
他的产品和饮料是最好的
His products and drinks are the best.
这是我们公司的总裁
This is the president of our company.
这是我们的客户，乔先生
This is our client, Mr. Jo.
很高兴见到你，总统先生
Nice to meet you, Mr. President.
我是总统
I'm the president.
这不是 Hyper 吗？
Isn't this Hyper?
我听说日本出了点问题
I heard there's a problem in Japan.
现在很难得到了
It's hard to get it now.
问他们要点钱没关系
It's okay to ask them for a few dollars.
价格比日本低
The price is lower than in Japan.
你能卖多少？
How much can you sell?
你能买多少？
How much can you buy this?
娇威，你人真好
Jiao Wei, you're so nice.
你想要多少？
How much do you want?
我们要多少？
How much do we want?
我后天给你20公斤
I'll give you 20kg of it the day after tomorrow.
20公斤价值3000亿韩元
20kg is worth about 300 billion won.
你觉得怎么样？
What do you think?
好吧
Okay.
这是合同
This is the contract.
如果交易成功,
If this deal is successful,
我们可以继续做生意
we can keep the business going.
从现在起你可以指望我们了
You can count on us from now on.
剩下的交给我
I'll take care of the rest.
别担心
Don't worry.
他们会搞定海关的，别担心
They'll take care of the customs. Don't worry.
好了，走吧
Okay. Come on.
我们都是兄弟
We're all brothers.
这是闭路电视吗？
Is this the CCTV?
是的
Yes.
就是他带走了死去的高善日
He's the one who took the dead Ko Sun-il.
停，停
Stop. Stop.
你
You.
质量很差
The quality is bad.
带上俱乐部主席
Bring the club president.
是的
Yes.
你到底认不认识他？
Do you know him or not?
如果你不告诉他我在你店里卖毒品,
If you don't tell him that I sold drugs in your store,
我会骂你的
I'll scold you.
我不是说我不认识他
I'm not saying I don't know him.
我真的不认识他
I really don't know him.
那些混蛋想在不告诉老板的情况下卖毒品
Those bastards are trying to sell drugs without telling the boss.
我怎么知道？
How do I know that?
但是韩国警方
But the Korean police
不能逮捕这么重的人
can't arrest such a heavy person
未经允许就进行调查
and investigate it without permission.
这就是为什么人们说它是假的
That's why people say it's fake.
嘿，给我倒杯咖啡
Hey, get me a cup of coffee.
我？
Me?
是的，我在跟你说话
Yes, I'm talking to you.
嘿，小心点
Hey, be careful.
这家伙有大麻烦了
This guy is in big trouble.
不，不
No, no.
如果你再报道一次闭路电视，我就惩罚你
If you cover the CCTV one more time, I'll punish you.
那就让我们把真理之屋打扫干净
Then let's clean up the room of truth.
是时候清理一下了
It's time to clean up.
Park Rae-ah.
是的
Yes.
我不想这么做
I don't want to do it.
里面有很多灰尘
There's a lot of dust in there.
他怎么了？
What's wrong with him?
嘿，这样看著他
Hey, look at him like this.
嘿，嘿，嘿
Hey, hey, hey.
没事了，没事了
It's okay, it's okay.
坐直了，坐直了
Sit straight, sit straight.
你不舒服
You're not feeling well.
没事了，没事了
It's okay, it's okay.
现在，开始吧
Now, start.
我们的贵宾每周来一次
It's our VIP who comes once a week.
每次我来，我都会卖一个大的
Every time I come, I sell a big one.
即使加班，他们也假装不知道
They pretended not to know even if they were working overtime.
我不会卖的
I'm not going to sell it.
又来？
Again?
仅此而已
That's all.
我们再收拾一下
Let's clean up again.
等一下
Wait a minute.
求你了
Please.
好吧
Okay.
继续
Keep going.
他是最受欢迎的人
He's the most popular guy.
他从去年开始就是仁川的毒贩
He's a drug dealer from Incheon since last year.
我得到它是因为我有钱
I got it because I had money.
我们俱乐部不卖真正的毒品
Our club doesn't sell real drugs.
是真的
It's real.
不是在江南就是在仁川
It's either in Gangnam or Incheon.
我不知道
I don't know.
好吧
Okay.
把他交出来，打电话给通讯公司
Hey, hand him over and call the communications company.
找到 Hiroshi 的位置
Get the location of Hiroshi.
我会杀了首尔的毒贩子
I'll kill the drug dealers in Seoul.
谁要去仁川？
Who's going to Incheon?
我带孩子们去仁川
I'll take the kids to Incheon.
好吧，带他走
Okay, take him.
是的
Yes.
所以东宇说的是
So what Dong-woo said is
是的
Yes.
江南区的总统还在喷洒毒品
The president of Gangnam is still spraying drugs.
你就是这个意思
That's what you're saying.
那是富人的高级酒吧
It's a high-end bar for rich people.
只有会员才能参加
It's run by members only.
他还在那里喷洒秘密药物
He's spraying secret drugs there, too.
但我绝不会进去
But I'm never going in there.
郑总统的弟弟是黑社会
President Jung's brother is a gangster.
如果被抓到，我会死的
I'll die if I get caught.
总之，我把俱乐部弄坏了
Anyway, I broke the club.
多亏了你，我要逃跑了
Thanks to you, I'm running away.
如果我不让你去,
Hey, if I don't let you go there,
下次我就放你走
I'll let you go next time.
这是一，二，三，四
Here's one, two, three, four.
嘿，这里？
Hey, here?
是的
Yes.
门锁上了，你个混蛋
The door's locked, you bastard.
我不知道
I don't know that.
等等
Oh, wait a minute.
我进去
I'll go in.
没事的，你得去看看
It's okay. You have to check it out.
喂，车东云
Hey, Cha Dong-woon.
你好，俊秀
Hello, Junsu.
你怎么进来的？
How did you get in?
你们是什么人？
What are you guys?
你把门弄坏了吗？
Did you break the door?
去把门修好
Go and fix the door.
快点
Hurry up.
对不起
I'm sorry.
振洙，是谁？
Jin-su, who is it?
没什么
It's nothing.
我是来见荣格校长的
I'm here to see President Jung.
我妹妹是你的朋友吗？
Is my sister your friend?
出去
Get out.
冷静点
Calm down.
警徽..
The badge...
你疯了
You're out of your mind.
起来
Get up.
是警察
It's the police.
你是谁？
Who are you?
你凭什么毁了我的生意？
Who are you to ruin my business?
你到底是谁？
Who the hell are you?
是警察
It's the police.
郑会长？
President Jung?
你说你卖毒品
You said you sold drugs.
药呢？
Where's the medicine?
我都听到了
I heard everything.
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
等一下
Wait a minute.
别碰它
Don't touch it.
为什么这里有个抽屉？
Why is there a drawer here?
那里可能有个抽屉
There could be a drawer there.
发生什么事了？
What's going on?
不，告诉我
No, talk to me.
什么事？
Yes?
警探
Detective.
嘿，你难过吗? 坐直了
Hey, are you sad? Sit straight.
你怎么敢打警察，你这个混蛋
How dare you punch the police, you bastard.
如果你告诉我真相，我就让你上去
And if you tell me the truth, I'll let you go to the top.
快点告诉我
Tell me quickly.
事实上，我父亲在我小时候是个酒鬼
Actually, my father was an alcoholic when I was young.
嘿，嘿，嘿
Hey, hey, hey.
太吵了
Oh, it's loud.
你到底认不认识这个人？
Do you know this person or not?
看，看
Look, look.
Hee-ro 先生？
Oh, Mr. Hee-ro?
我每周去一次商店
I came to the store once a week.
起初，我在仁川遇见他
At first, I met him in Incheon.
药是从仁川运来的吗？
Is the medicine coming from Incheon?
他自己做的
He made it himself.
我听说他是从日本来的黑社会
I heard he's a gangster from Japan.
日本黑帮？
Yakuza?
兄弟，我查过 Hee-ro 在仁川
Brother, I checked that Hee-ro is here in Incheon.
我现在就去拿
I'll get it right now.
他是日本黑帮的
He's a Yakuza.
你会说日语吗？
Do you speak Japanese?
没有
No.
我会说日语
I'll speak Japanese.
我会处理的
I'll take care of it.
总之，小心点
Anyway, be careful.
我应该去吗？
Should I have gone?
是谁？
Who is it?
嗯..
Um...
这是什么样的疯子？
What kind of crazy bastard is it?
你这个混蛋！
You bastard!
拦住他！
Stop him!
你没事吧？
Are you okay?
我要死了
I'm dying.
这是什么？
What's this?
你们这些混蛋！
You bastards!
你从哪儿弄来的？
Where did you get this?
这是警用枪
This is a police gun.
你不会说韩语吗？
Can't you speak Korean?
你在笑吗？
Are you laughing?
你吸毒，杀人
You're taking drugs and killing people.
我会让你做这做那至少30年
I'll make you do this and that for at least 30 years.
你笑是因为你明白这一点
You're laughing because you understand this.
队长，我来了
Team leader, I'm here.
Seok-do！
Seok-do!
怎么了？
What's up?
我要上去抓 Hee-won
I'm going up to catch Hee-won.
干得好
Good job.
你们以为抓不到我吗？
You guys thought you wouldn't catch me?
这混蛋家里还有很多毒品
There's a lot of drugs left in this bastard's house.
超过20公斤
It's over 20kg.
这次我会抓住你的
I'm going to catch you this time.
干得好
Good job.
我上去..
I'll go up and...
喂？
Hello?
嘿！
Hey!
别丢下我！
Don't leave me!
带我一起走！
Take me with you!
哥哥，你把浩看得很好
Brother, you watched Hiroshi well.
Tomo 怎么办？
What about Tomo?
我联系了他
I contacted him.
我要杀了你
I'm going to kill you.
嘿，你在干什么？
Hey, what are you doing?
我从没见过你
I've never seen you before.
嘿，你不教你的孩子吗？
Hey, don't you teach your kids?
不！
No!
住手！
Stop it!
你为什么要这样对我？
Why are you doing this to me?
你疯了吗? 你从警察那里偷药？
Are you crazy? You're stealing medicine from the police?
如果李哲珠主席知道了，我们都会死的
If Chairman Lee Chil-joo finds out, we'll all die.
我们会因为偷毒品被抓的
We'll get caught for stealing the drugs.
那就别让她发现
Then, don't let her find out.
如果我们这次搞砸了,
If we mess up this time,
你们都会死
you'll all die.
这是明天和白总的交易
This is a deal with CEO Baek tomorrow.
再包一次
Pack it again.
没收20公斤毒品
20kg of drug is confiscated.
价格是三百万韩元
The price is 3 million won.
这边请
This way.
别碰我
Don't touch me.
我来吧
I'll do it.
钟书记！
Secretary Jong!
哦，天啊
Oh, my.
坐下
Sit down.
你没事吧？
Are you okay?
发生什么事了？
What happened?
对不起
I'm sorry.
你抱歉什么？
What are you sorry for?
你没事吧？
Are you okay?
我们没事
We're okay.
We're fine.
泰秀呢？
What about Tae-su?
他在急诊室
He's in the emergency room.
他的头伤得很重
He's hurt his head a lot.
哦，天啊
Oh, my.
如果你今天想把这些都发出去,
If you want to send all of this today,
你得快点
you have to hurry.
天哪，今天是蓝蟹吗？
Oh, my. Is it blue crab today?
闻起来很可疑
It smells fishy.
放进去
Put it deep inside.
什么？
What?
你好，好久不见
Hello. Long time no see.
什么？
What?
你现在就来吗？
You're coming now?
哦，是的
Oh, yes.
嗨
Hi.
嘿，Tomo 来了
Hey, Tomo is coming.
那个狗娘养的
That son of a bitch.
他说他会来的
He said he was coming.
但我准备了很多
But I prepared a lot.
生意..
Business is...
什么? 他已经来了？
What? He's already here?
他为什么这么快？
Why is he so fast?
他平时动作很慢
He's usually so slow.
欢迎来到日本
Welcome to Japan.
这次我要打开
I'm going to open this time.
怎么样，找到了吗？
How did it go? Did you find it?
再看看这个
Check this again.
这是什么? 一团糟
What is this? It's a total mess.
这事很紧急，所以赶紧收拾干净
It's urgent, so wrap it up clean.
我听说 Hee-ro 死了
I heard that Hee-ro is dead.
我们的生意有什么问题吗？
Isn't there a problem with our business?
说话注意点
Watch your mouth.
就算你逼我，你也不知道
You don't know even if you make me do it.
你不知道，你明白吗？
You don't know. Do you understand?
我明白
I understand.
你负责处理 Hee-ro 的尸体
You're in charge of the dead Hee-ro.
我已经和我的搭档谈过了
I've already finished talking to my partner.
真的吗，太棒了！
Really? Awesome!
那你不该把我介绍给你的搭档吗？
Then shouldn't you introduce me to your partner?
你不知道
You don't know.
听我说
Just listen to me.
我不需要知道
Yeah, I don't have to know.
我只是需要赚钱
I just need to make money.
嘿，包起来给他
Hey, wrap it up and give it to him.
这条鳗鱼不错
Hey, this eel is good.
多吃点，早日康复
Eat a lot and get better soon.
谢谢，谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
但你什么都没看见？
But you didn't see anything?
监控录像拍到你晕倒了
CCTVs around you fainted.
我觉得他一开始就在跟踪我们
I think he followed us in the first place.
嘿，你吃东西的时候为什么跟我说话？
Hey, why are you talking to me when you're eating?
嘿，吃了它
Hey, eat it.
你不知道印象的不同吗？
You don't know the impression difference?
是的，太黑了
Yes, it was too dark.
我吃完再吃
I'll eat it later after I eat.
你为什么不吃? 很好吃，对吧？
Why don't you eat? It's delicious, right?
嘿！
Hey!
东姑，你在干什么？
Dong-gu, what are you doing?
我是来工作的，你没什么事吧？
I'm here for work. You didn't have anything to do, did you?
是啊，是啊
Yeah, yeah.
这是和我一起工作的哥哥
This is my brother who worked with me.
我很久没来这里了
It's been a while since I've been here.
很高兴认识你
Nice to meet you.
我叫黄东固，是北方的毒贩子
I'm Hwang Dong-gu, a drug dealer in the North.
我是宫泰日
I'm Gong Tae-il.
发生什么事了？
What's going on?
你能看看这个吗？
Can you take a look at this?
这是什么？
What is this?
你知道这个吗？
Hey, do you know this?
我想我们是从 Hee-ro 家拿的
I think we took it from Hee-ro's house.
我要了
I'll take it.
是的，这是我们队长的枪
Yes, this is our team leader's gun.
我们的队长
Our team leader
他已经失踪好几天了
It's been a few days since he went missing.
他失踪了？
He's missing?
我们的队长也调查了超光速
Our team leader also investigated the hyper.
原来是个警察局
It was originally a police station.
我们的队长一直说有点不对劲
Our team leader keeps saying something's weird.
我觉得他一直在单独调查和日本黑帮有点纠葛
I think he's been investigating separately and got a little tangled up with the Yakuza.
日本黑帮什么时候开始的？
When did the Yakuza start?
给你
Here you go.
据我的线人说,
According to my informant,
三年前，日本黑帮和白相狼
Three years ago, the Yakuza and the White Sang-upa
他们联合起来，向超能力者喷射
They're united and sprayed the hyper.
但两年前,
But two years ago,
两个白相狼被杀了
Two of the White Sang-upa were killed.
当时，栗永西正宗大
At that time, the Kuryongseo Masoo Dae
我把所有的白人都叫来了
I got all the white Sang-upa guys.
我看不到药
I couldn't see the medicine.
但是黑帮的人和谁在一起
But who the Yakuza guys were with.
这艘飞船又开始旋转了
This hyper started to spin again.
谁是负责这件事的警探？
Who's the detective in charge of this?
没有，但我去了别人的公司
No, but I came to someone else's company.
我要你给我看调查记录
I'm asking you to show me the investigation record.
是不是有点？
Isn't it a little bit?
没有，但这是队长
No, but here's the team leader.
有人告诉我要做好工作
I was told to do a good job.
白相霸
White Sang-upa.
他一个人进去，解决了所有问题
He went in alone and solved everything.
有两支特种部队
There are two special forces.
我会说些奇怪的话吗？
Would I say something weird?
嗯
Uh.
抱歉让你久等了
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
我是朱松哲，毒品调查组的组长
I'm Ju Sung-chul, the team leader of the Drug Investigation Unit.
是的，我是马锡道
Yes, I'm Ma Seok-do.
你是光州人？
You're from Gwangsu-do?
是的，我是 Kim Man-jae
Yes, I'm Kim Man-jae.
是的
Yes.
请坐
Please sit.
是的
Yes.
请坐
Please sit.
我听说员工出事了
I heard that the employees were in an accident.
我好难过
I'm so upset.
我们必须除掉这些坏蛋
We have to get rid of these bad guys.
这就是我来这里的原因
That's why I came here.
我听说这和日本黑帮有关
I heard that this is related to the Yakuza.
你有什么能告诉我的吗？
Is there anything you can tell me?
我们还在调查
We're still investigating.
但是有很多事情我们还没有确认
But there are a lot of things that we haven't confirmed yet.
所以我不能什么都告诉你
So I can't tell you everything.
我想看看我儿子的脸
I want to see my son's face.
我知道
I know.
我也想看看他的脸
I want to see his face, too.
那我们得快点了
Then we should hurry up.
等等
Wait.
我觉得我们陷得太深了
I think we went too deep.
别说了
Let's stop.
对不起，我们有机会再来
I'm sorry, but we'll come back when we have a chance.
没关系
It's okay.
我不舒服
I'm uncomfortable.
伙计们
You guys.
交给我们吧
Please leave it to us.
有发现我们会通知你的
We'll call you if we find anything.
是的，长官
Yes, sir.
等等
Wait.
为什么？
Why?
你认识郑京植吗，北方的队长？
Do you know Jeong Kyung-sik, the team leader of the North?
他失踪了
He's missing.
嘿
Hey.
谁？
Who?
郑京植
Jeong Kyung-sik.
你是说北境的队长吗？
You mean the team leader of the North?
作为一名警察，我很抱歉这么说
I'm sorry to say this as a police officer.
他有问题
He had a problem.
什么问题？
What problem?
我们有保安
We're under security.
我不能告诉你细节
I can't tell you in detail.
这不是你的案子
It's not your case.
我觉得再问下去很不礼貌
I think it's rude to ask you any more.
你很敏感
You're sensitive.
嘿
Hey.
别说了
Stop.
好吧
Okay.
然后..
Then...
如果你发现了什么，请联系我们
If you find anything, please contact us.
就这么办
Let's do that.
是的
Yes.
是的，谢谢
Yes, thank you.
谢谢你
Thank you.
嘿，嘿，嘿，名片变了，我给错你了
Hey, hey, hey, the business card has changed. I gave it to you wrong.
不，不，别走，反正我也不会联系你
No, no, don't go. I'm not going to contact you anyway.
他为什么要联系你？
Why would he contact you?
你去吗？
Are you going?
哦，该死
Oh, shit.
你会还给我吗？
Are you going to give it back?
不，我给了他一张中国名片
No, I gave him a Chinese business card.
去吧
Go.
我觉得他们有什么不舒服的地方
I think they're uncomfortable with something.
我让你不舒服了
I made you uncomfortable.
我只是觉得你是个好人
I just saw that you're a good person.
你喜欢什么？
What do you like?
他和我一样英俊潇洒，但他感觉不太好
He's handsome and handsome like me, but he doesn't feel good.
为什么? 什么？
Why? What?
我什么都没说
I didn't say anything.
对了，副经理让我给你打电话
Oh, right. The deputy manager asked me to call you.
为什么？
Why?
我必须在正式程序之后进行调查
I have to investigate after the formal procedure.
他告诉我不要这样走来走去
He told me not to go around like this.
我觉得副经理对你了解太多了
I think the deputy manager knows too much about you.
我太了解了
I know too well.
但是如果你这么做，你会错过所有的罪犯
But if you do that, you'll miss all the criminals.
是啊，东姑，东姑
Yeah, Dong-gu, Dong-gu.
你跟我说的那些信息呢？
Where's the information you told me about?
我在车里
I'm in the car.
嘿，今天吃肉，明天睡个好觉
Hey, have a meat meal today and sleep well tomorrow.
是的
Yes.
你收到我寄给你的东西了吗？
Did you get all the goods I sent you?
我会好好洗的
I'll wash it well.
我要走了
I'm going.
那是什么鬼东西？
What the hell is that?
你要去哪里？
Where are you going?
嘿！
Hey!
下车！
Get out of the car!
你打算怎么办？
What are you going to do?
下车！
Get out of the car!
怎么了，不管用吗？
What? It's not working?
别这么做
Don't do it.
他把香肠塞进耳朵里了吗？
Did he put a sausage in his ear?
嘿！
Hey!
下车！
Get out of the car!
你健身了吗？
Did you work out?
你是 Chorong 对吧？
You're Chorong, right?
佐荣？
Chorong?
你是个粗鲁的混蛋
You're a rude bastard.
我以前是个武术运动员
I used to be a martial arts player.
如果你不想死，就走吧
If you don't want to die, just go.
别傻了
Don't be a fool.
上车
Get in the car.
我们走吧
Let's go.
我该怎么办？
What should I do?
我应该上台阶吗？
Should I step on the step?
别这么做！
Don't do it!
你不能打一个正常人！
You can't hit a normal person!
上车
Get in the car.
我好尴尬
I'm so embarrassed.
你会惹上麻烦的
You'll get in trouble.
我下手太重了
I hit him too hard.
嘿！
Hey!
他睡著了吗？
Is he sleeping?
醒醒！
Wake up!
嘿！
Hey!
呼吸！
Breathe!
他没事吧？
Is he okay?
我去叫醒他
I'll wake him up.
你没事吧？
Are you okay?
他是真的白相浩吗？
Is he the real Baek Sang-ho?
是你吗？
Is it you?
他长得像我，但他是真人
He looks like me, but he's the real one.
我们应该早点来的
We should have come earlier.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你经营二手车生意，还经营这个俱乐部？
So you run a used car business and run this club?
是的
Yes.
我听说棒球运动员经常来你经营的俱乐部
I heard that baseball players come to the club you run often.
棒球运动员在那里卖毒品吗？
Do baseball players sell drugs there?
Tomo 每个周末都带日本人来
Tomo brings Japanese people every weekend.
他贩毒，打人
He sells drugs and beats people.
给你
Here.
Tomo？
Tomo?
是的
Yes.
Tomo 在左边
Tomo on the left.
Tomo.
他现在在哪？
Where is he now?
他可能周五会在俱乐部表演
He's probably playing in the club on Friday.
停在前面
Stop in front.
我会告诉负责他的医生
I'll tell the MD in charge of him.
他是个翻译
He's a translator.
如果他不跟警探走，就会被捅死
He gets stabbed if he doesn't go with the detective.
如果你不跟他走，你会再次被刺伤
If you don't go with him, you'll get stabbed again.
真的吗？
Really?
快点
Hurry up.
嘿，汤姆是个笨蛋
Hey, Tom's stupid.
他在说毒品，还说他很蠢
He's talking about drugs and saying he's stupid.
你不是韩国人就是中国人
You're either Korean or Chinese.
处理掉
Get rid of it.
我们到了
We're here.
我一找到药就回来
I'll be back as soon as I find the medicine.
他现在在哪？
Where is he now?
我现在联系不上他
I can't get in touch with him right now.
我清理完就回来
I'll be back after I clean up.
我们去韩国分公司吧
Let's go to the South Korean branch.
是的
Yes.
你怎么还不来？
Why aren't you here yet?
我有点迟到了
I'm a little late.
也许晚点吧
Maybe a little later.
我已经计划好了
I already made the plan.
你让我很为难
You're making it hard for me.
是的
Yes.
你在哪里？
Where are you?
有个问题
There's a problem.
该组织的一名成员要求李志照主席把药拿走
A member of the organization asked Chairman Lee Chi-jo to take away the medicine.
那又怎样？
So?
Lee Chi-jo 派了辆车去韩国
Lee Chi-jo sent a carjavil to Korea.
我想有些已经在路上了
I think some of them are already on the way.
那又怎样？
So?
他是真实存在的
He's real.
我要躲一会儿，看看情况
I'm going to hide for a while and watch the situation.
如果你做错了什么，你会死的
If you do something wrong, you'll die.
我有药作为保险
I have the medicine as insurance.
好吧
All right.
是的，看起来不太对
Yes, it doesn't seem right.
没什么
It's nothing.
再给我两天时间
Give me two more days.
如果到时候我还没看到货,
If I don't see the goods by then,
我就不能说得这么好了
I won't be able to speak so well.
我们不认识他们
We don't know them.
你算什么警察？
What kind of police are you?
啊！
Ugh!
汤姆呢？
Where is Tom?
我不知道
I don't know.
你怎么在后门？
Hey, why are you at the back door?
正如你承诺的，我和这个案子没有任何关系
As you promised, I have nothing to do with this case
好了，快点
Okay, hurry up
C 球俱乐部是什么意思？
What does C-Ball Club mean?
是个网络俱乐部
It's a cyber club
嘿，咪咪
Hey, Mimi
嘿，挂电话
Hey, hang up
挂电话
Hang up
你又中枪了吗？
Did you get hit again?
不，日本人来了
No, the Japanese are here
你今天又犯浑了
You're being a jerk again today
好吧
Oh, well...
你今天又犯浑了
You're being a jerk again today
我来处理，你们先进去
I'll take care of it, so take the guys inside
没有
No
我有点紧张
I'm a little nervous
嘿，别这么说
Hey, don't say that
伙计们，跟著咪咪到前门
Guys, follow Mimi to the front door
跟我来
Follow me
嘿，去后门
Hey, go to the back door
是的，长官
Yes, sir
我是 Agarito
I'm Agarito
是的，就是这里
Yes, this is the right place
谢谢你
Thank you
C 球
C-Ball
对不起
I'm sorry.
就是这个
Here it is.
干杯！
Cheers!
我突然胃痛
I suddenly have a stomachache.
你不是警察
Hey, you're not a police officer.
我们是警察
We're police officers.
这里有个叫波莫的人
There's a guy named Pomo here.
怎么了？
What's wrong?
我不明白你在说什么
I don't understand what you're saying.
怎么了？
What's wrong?
别动
Don't move.
你是谁？
Who are you?
你是个警察
You're a police officer.
你不明白我在说什么，对吧？
You don't understand what I'm saying, do you?
你为什么要搬家？
Why are you moving?
嘿，嘿，嘿，上车，上车
Hey, hey, hey, get the car. Get the car.
什么? 嘿，你这个混蛋
What? Hey, you bastard.
Tomo 在哪？
Where is Tomo?
对不起
I'm sorry.
嘿，你躲起来了吗？
Hey, are you hiding?
出来
Come out.
Tomo 在哪？
Where is Tomo?
这是个混蛋
This is a bastard.
别打我
Don't hit me.
我不认为 Tomo 在这里
I don't think Tomo is here.
Tomo 在哪？
Where is Tomo?
我在松柏饭店
I'm at the Songbo Hotel.
好吧，到酒店来
Okay, come to the hotel.
嘿！
Hey!
又是你？
You again?
是我
It's me.
该死，你背叛了我
Damn it. You betrayed me.
你看起来像是被打了一顿
You look like you've been beaten up.
什么？
What?
我被 Chuseok 党的领袖威胁了
I was threatened by the head of the Chuseok party.
我会解决的
I'll solve it.
主席，你很生气
Chairman, you're angry.
把药给我
Give me the medicine.
Tomo 在吗？
Is Tomo here?
是的，他在这里
Yes, he's here.
旅馆的地址是什么？
What's the address of the hotel?
现在是1610年
It's 1610.
嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
跑，跑，跑
Run, run, run.
我现在启动不了！
I can't start it right now!
哦，天哪！
Oh, my!
怎么了？
What's wrong?
哦，天哪！
Oh, my!
嘿，这是我老婆的车！
Hey, it's my wife's car!
是日本黑帮的一具尸体
It's a body from the Yakuza.
谁干的？
Who did it?
车牌号是多少？
What's the car number?
车牌号..
The car number...
我都查过了
I checked both of them.
我觉得是个枪手
I think it's a gunman.
酒店的闭路电视上有这张脸的照片
There's a picture of the face on the CCTV at the hotel.
我去看看
I'll take a look at it.
好吧
Okay.
你还好吗，你还好吗？
Are you okay? Are you okay?
在那儿吗？
Is it there?
这里吗？
Here?
哦，天哪！
Oh, my!
光头党先来了
The Gwangsu-dae is here first.
就是这个混蛋，带走 Tomo 的混蛋
It's this bastard. The bastard who took Tomo.
他就是 Tomo 说的那个人
He's the one Tomo was talking about.
从日本来的那个
The one who came from Japan.
他不在酒店
He's not in the hotel.
那他们为什么在那里？
Then why are they there?
那些 Gwangsu 的混蛋在找 Tomo
Those bastards from Gwangsu are looking for Tomo.
因为那个混蛋，事情会变得一团糟
Things are going to be a mess because of that bastard.
队长，白先生怎么说？
Team leader, what did Mr. Baek say?
我们该怎么办？
What should we do?
我们先找到这个混蛋
Let's find this bastard first.
我再问你一次
I'll ask you again.
你给我的药呢？
Where is the medicine you gave me?
如果我现在告诉你，你会杀了我的
If I tell you now, you'll kill me.
如果你放我走，我就把药给你
If you let me go, I'll give you the medicine.
那又怎样？
So?
你也是去拿药的
You were there for the medicine, too.
怎么样? 30亿
How is it? It's 3 billion.
我是唯一一个知道破针价格的人
I'm the only one who knows the price of a broken needle.
是的
Yes.
真的吗？
Really?
是的
Yes.
我会用我的生命去找到它
I'll find it with my life.
找到所有有药的地方
Find all the places with medicine.
Chuseoncheol 呢？
What about Chuseoncheol?
春秋..
Chuseoncheol...
你个白痴
You idiot.
如果你发现了什么，告诉我
If you find anything else, let me know.
是的，长官
Yes, sir.
Tomo 死了？
Hey, Tomo is dead?
是的，长官
Yes, sir.
你看到的那些人是在钓鱼点被杀的
The guys you saw were killed at the fishing spot.
我们该怎么办? 情况失控了
What should we do? It's getting out of hand.
该死
Darn it.
我们应该抓住他们的
We should've caught them.
还有别的地方吗？
Is there any other place?
有点..
It's a bit...
很奇怪，不是吗？
Weird, isn't it?
我来是因为他是常客
I came because he's a regular.
我们不是在正式调查
We're not officially investigating.
嘿
Hey.
哦，不
Oh, no.
什么意思，我什么都没说
What do you mean? I didn't say anything.
是的，长官
Yes, sir.
什么意思？
What do you mean?
我不知道
I don't know.
你不知道? 过来
You don't know? Come here.
过来，我告诉你
Come here. I'll tell you.
坐这儿
Sit here.
是的，长官
Yes, sir.
嘿
Hey.
是的，长官
Yes, sir.
如果我问你，请快点回答
Answer me quickly if I ask you.
是的，长官
Yes, sir.
你拉在裤子上了
You're pooping on your pants.
这些裤子是什么？
What are these pants?
我从柜台借的
I borrowed them from the counter.
我告诉过你不要打我的肚子
I told you not to hit my stomach.
嘿，把灯打开，怎么这么黑？
Hey, turn on the light. Why is it so dark?
是的，长官
Yes, sir.
我来打开
I'll turn it on.
不，我..
No, I...
嘿
Hey.
是的，长官
Yes, sir.
你的日本黑帮呢？
Where's your yakuza?
嘿
Hey.
这有什么问题吗？
What's wrong with this?
嘿，关掉
Hey, turn it off.
取消了
It's off.
关不掉
It's not turning off.
开始了
It's on.
怎么了？
What's wrong?
对不起
I'm sorry.
又开始了
It's on again.
我得脱掉外套
I have to take off my coat.
嘿
Hey.
你怎么处理日本黑帮的？
What do you do with yakuza?
我不会做像日本黑帮那样的坏事
I don't do anything bad like yakuza.
我只负责分发和包装药品
I just distribute and pack the medicine.
我只负责送货
I just deliver it.
这是坏事，你这个罪犯
That's a bad thing, you criminal.
你知道有多少人因为你的药死了吗？
Do you know how many people died because of your medicine?
我不知道
I don't know.
那你见过这个人吗？
Then, have you seen this person?
仔细看
Look carefully.
我不知道
I don't know.
你不知道？
You don't know?
没有
No.
那是谁袭击了警探？
Then, who's the one who hit the detectives?
我不知道
I don't know.
你不知道？
You don't know?
什么？
What?
嘿，我做不到，关上门
Hey, I can't do this. Close the door.
是的，长官
Yes, sir.
不，不
No, no.
给他机会的时候要诚实
Be honest when you give him a chance.
等等
Wait.
那我去叫救护车
Then, I'll call an ambulance.
我现在就打
I'll call it now.
等等，等等
Wait, wait, wait.
我不知道是谁袭击了警探
I don't know who hit the detectives.
但据我所知,
But, as far as I know,
不是日本黑帮
it's not yakuza.
还有别人
There's someone else.
日本黑帮的同伙
Yakuza's partner.
还有别人吗？
Someone else?
谁？
Who?
嘿，你！
Hey, you!
你们这些混蛋！
You bastards!
因为你我才能赚钱
I'm making money because of you.
你怎么敢这么说？
How dare you say that?
过来
Come here.
你这个叛徒！
You traitor!
是谁杀了 Tomo？
Who's the one who killed Tomo?
里奇
Ricky.
里奇？
Ricky?
里奇
Ricky.
是他把我送到这家医院的
He's the one who sent me to this hospital.
他带药来了吗？
Did he bring the medicine?
我不知道
I don't know.
你不知道？
You don't know?
我不知道
I don't know.
搭档呢？
Where's the partner?
我真的不知道
I really don't know.
我在找里奇
I'm looking for Ricky.
我在找他！
I'm looking for him!
Tomo 把药藏在哪儿了？
Where did Tomo hide the medicine?
去告诉里奇
Go tell Ricky.
如果他碰了那药，我就杀了你
If he touches that drug, I'll kill you.
警探们，你们做了这么多调查
Wow, detectives, you've done so much research.
为什么没有我的照片？
Why isn't there a picture of me?
嘿，你来了
Hey, you're here.
哦，是的
Oh, yes.
嘿，那么
Hey, then.
是的
Yes.
这个问号就是那个带走我们孩子，拿走毒品的人吗？
Is that question mark the one who took our kids and took the drugs?
也许吧
Maybe.
宝贝？
Baby?
当 Tomo 从日本带来所有的原材料时,
When Tomo brings all the raw materials from Japan,
日本黑帮的孩子们开始合成并喷洒它
The Yakuza kids start to synthesize and spray it.
这个问号就是为此准备的
This question mark was looking after that.
嘿，那么
Hey, then.
是的
Yes.
里奇，你认识这个人吗？
Ricky, do you know this guy?
我以前从没见过
I've never seen it before.
嘿，嘿
Hey, hey.
看看这个
Look at this.
这是一份来自日本的公开文件
It's a public document from Japan.
什么？
What?
我真的要这么做吗？
Do I really do it?
你是最棒的，所以你来吧
You're the best at them, so you do it.
哦，是的
Oh, yes.
叫里奇
Name Ricky.
立即解决李志钊主席的危机
The immediate solution to Chairman Lee Chi-jo's crisis.
他在你们组织里以刀工闻名
Famous for his knife work in your organization.
他刚刚扔了个手榴弹
He threw a grenade a while ago.
那他为什么来韩国？
Then why did he come to Korea?
我不知道
I don't know.
你又不知道？
You don't know again?
哦，天啊
Oh, my.
为什么？
Why?
就是这样
That's it.
Tomo 用问号策划并偷走了毒品
Tomo planned with the question mark and stole the drugs.
你为什么把20公斤藏起来？
Why are you holding back the 20-kilograms?
里奇来韩国找它
Ricky came to Korea to find it.
然后里奇会找到毒品
Then Ricky's going to find the drugs.
你可以用那个问号
You could go to that question mark.
嘿，嘿
Hey, hey.
都搞定了
It's all done.
一次抓住他们所有人
Just catch them all at once.
我们先找到毒品
Let's find the drugs first.
哦，我的天啊
Oh, my God.
不出所料，我们的兄弟
As expected, our brother.
你疯了吗？
Are you crazy?
处理掉
Get rid of it.
你必须抓住坏人
You have to catch the bad guys.
你要去哪里？
Where are you going?
哦，我的手臂
Oh, my arm.
Seok-doo，你现在在哪里？
Seok-doo, where are you now?
我会这么做的
I'll do it that way.
不，你不能因为受伤就一直走
No, you can't keep moving because you're hurt.
他们杀了人
Hey, they killed a man.
我必须把他们都抓住
I have to catch them all.
我会把他们都抓起来，这样你就可以放松了
I'll catch them all, so you can relax.
你能做到吗？
Can you do that?
如果你等我，我就在那儿
I'll be there if you wait.
哦，我的天啊
Oh, my God.
嘿
Hey.
什么事？
Yes?
我要去抓队长，打电话给孩子们，别让他们过来
I'm going to catch the team leader, so call the kids and keep them from coming.
是的，是的
Yes, yes.
好冷
Oh, it's cold.
你找到药了吗？
Did you find the medicine?
你没有吧？
You didn't, right?
看到没，我说了我办公室里没有
See? I told you I didn't have it in my office.
我很抱歉这么说,
And I'm sorry to say this,
但当车里有人的时候,
but when there's someone in the car,
你得把窗户打开一点
you have to open the window a little.
否则就会窒息而死
Otherwise, it can be a suffocation.
这个案子结束之前你是不会死的
Hey, you'll never die until this case is over.
嘿，有没有什么地方能找到药？
Hey, is there any place you can find the medicine?
你去过 Tomo 的伪装办公室吗？
Have you been to Tomo's disguise office?
喂，东姑
Hey, Dong-gu.
我发现了蓝队队长的尸体
I found the body of the chief of the Blue Team.
渔民在矿井的垃圾场找到的
The fishermen found it in the dump of the mine.
我认为他马上就杀了那个失踪的党员
I think he killed the missing party member right away.
但他被捕时还活著
But he was alive when he was arrested.
哇，疯狂的混蛋
Wow, crazy bastards.
他们甚至杀了警察
They even killed the police.
他们是疯子
They're crazy bastards.
你在哪里？
Where are you?
我在搜查 Tomo 的办公室
I'm searching Tomo's office.
找到杨
Find Yang.
你把它藏哪儿了？
Where did you hide it?
你叫什么名字？
What's your name?
你有枪吗？
Do you have a gun?
里奇？
Ricky?
你在找药吗？
Are you looking for a medicine?
你说什么呢？
What are you talking about?
如果你再靠近，我就杀了你
Hey, if you come close, I'll kill you.
PikaHD.com
求你了
Please.
我收到了贺卡
I received the greeting card.
我听说你在对你的朋友做坏事
I heard you're doing bad things to your friends.
因为你拿出来的药，主席很不舒服
The chairman is very uncomfortable because of the medicine you took out.
你犯了个错误
You made a mistake.
我应该立刻杀了你
I should have killed you at once.
主席的错误在于我不能杀死他
The chairman's mistake was that I couldn't kill him.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我不是故意的
I didn't mean to.
我帮你赚了很多钱
I've made you a lot of money.
我需要照顾好自己
I need to take care of myself.
或者你可以买下来
Or you can buy it.
我必须付出代价
I have to pay.
你麻烦大了
You're in a lot of trouble.
你在跟谁说话？
Who are you talking to?
你没钱
You don't have the money.
这药是主席的
The medicine is the chairman's.
随便你
Do whatever you want.
让我们看看会发生什么
Let's see what happens.
你说什么？
What did you say?
我很期待
I'm looking forward to it.
我觉得里奇接管了组织
I think Ricky took over the organization.
那药呢？
What about the medicine?
没有药
There's no medicine.
他几小时后要和白总统谈判
He's dealing with President Baek in a few hours.
我们该怎么办？
What should we do?
什么意思？
What do you mean?
我们得见个面
We have to meet.
什么？
What?
我会直接告诉你
I'll tell you directly.
让开
Move.
你以为你能骗得了我吗？
You think you can fool me?
我不再需要你了！
I don't need you anymore!
主席要买我的药
The chairman is buying my medicine.
- 怎么了?-这里是总务办公室
What is it? This is the general affairs office.
肯定有什么事
Something must be going on.
哦，谢谢我来自光苏大学
Oh, thank you. I'm from Gwangsu University.
- 那边怎么回事?-是个谋杀案
What's going on over there? It's a murder case.
受害者是一名警官
The victim is a police officer.
警察? 看看这个
Police? Look at this.
李刚浩? 他是周成哲手下的警察
Lee Gang-ho? He was the police officer under Joo Sung-chul.
他用锤子把墙敲碎了
He broke the wall with a hammer.
受害者一定是在找什么东西
The victim must have been looking for something.
他什么时候死的？
What time did he die?
凌晨两点左右
Around 2 a.m.
我们走吧
Let's go.
安静！
Be quiet!
那个混蛋
That bastard.
头儿，总部要开始内部调查了
Boss, the head office is going to start the internal investigation.
你们这些混蛋
You bastards.
我们找到药就走吧
Let's find the medicine and leave.
里奇肯定在找它
Ricky must be looking for it.
你就这么放著不管吗？
Are you just going to leave it?
杀了他
Just kill him.
快点交出你的位置
Hurry up and give up your position here.
你也应该完成你的工作
You should finish your work too.
我为什么要辞职？
Why should I give up my position?
我会负责的
I'll take responsibility.
你不打我就揍你，你疯了吗？
I'll beat you up if you don't. Are you crazy?
你疯了吗，混蛋？
Are you crazy, you bastard?
朱成哲的队长在吗？
Is the head of Joo Sung-chul's team here?
不，他不是，你可以走了
No, he's not. You can go.
他说他不在
He said he's not here.
他不在这里
He's not here.
好吧，我下次再来
Okay, I'll come back next time.
你可以直接问他
You can just ask him.
问他什么？
Ask him what?
等等
Wait.
你真烦人
You're so annoying.
什么？
What?
我问你点事
Let me ask you something.
没有
No.
为什么李江浩会在黎明的时候去总公司？
Why did Lee Kang-ho go to the head office at dawn?
你可以等他来了再问他
You can ask him when he's here.
我怎么知道? 他一定是去调查了
How would I know? He must have gone to investigate.
对
Right.
那时候？
At that time?
是的
Yes.
什么？
What?
他去拿药了吗？
Did he go to get the medicine?
没有
No.
你认识我吗？
Do you know me?
没有
No.
你认识我吗？
Do you know me?
你不能说
You can't say it.
你在总部
You're in the head office.
你不能说
You can't say it.
什么？
What?
你想干什么？
What do you want to do?
等等
Wait.
如果你继续碰他，他会受伤的
If you keep touching him, he'll get hurt.
你为什么要打扰别人的公司？
Why are you bothering someone else's company?
你会惹上麻烦的
You'll get in trouble.
我想我会再见到你的，别放松
I think I'll see you again. Don't relax.
如果你再发一次誓，我就杀了你
If you swear one more time, I'll kill you.
照个 X 光
Take an X-ray.
你的手
Your hand.
嘿
Hey.
是不是很奇怪？
Isn't it weird?
他们怎么了？
What's wrong with them?
对
Right.
但是在没有证据的情况下使用新闻不是很奇怪吗？
But isn't it weird to use the news without evidence?
我们得找到确凿的证据
We need to find something for sure.
等等
Wait.
有个富家子弟以前经营的游艇生意
There's a yacht business that rich kids used to run.
没有
No.
关门了
It's closed.
没有
No.
我们去那里
Let's go there.
走？
Go?
好吧
Okay.
我把地址给你
I'll give you the address.
干得好
Good job.
继续这样想
Keep thinking like that.
我知道了
I got it.
干得好
Good job.
我们走吧
Let's go.
好吧
Okay.
我去叫导游
I'll call the guide.
好吧
Okay.
怎么了，坐直了
What's okay? Sit straight.
好吧
Okay.
我希望他们晚点再打开窗户
I hope they open the window later.
我觉得还在施工中
I think it's under construction.
嘿！
Hey!
你是谁？
Who are you?
回家吧，我不干
Go home. I'm not doing it.
出去
Get out.
我们得进去，我们得报警
We have to go in. We have to call the police.
滚出去！
Get out!
嘿! 别这样！
Hey! Don't do it!
车里的人是你，对吧？
It was you in the car, right?
什么? 已经结束了？
What? It's already over?
紧急情况！
Emergency!
给我
Give it to me.
躺下
Lie down.
嘿，翻译
Hey, interpreter.
你为什么在这里？
Why are you here?
你不能来这里
You can't come here.
我们是来找解药的
We're here to find a cure.
你应该用敬语说
You should say it in honorifics.
我们是来找解药的
We're here to find a cure.
你是来找解药的，对吧？
You're here to find a cure, right?
药呢？
Where's the medicine?
医生是谁？
Who's the doctor?
我不知道
I don't know.
你不知道？
You don't know?
如果你撒谎，你会死的
You'll die if you lie.
药呢？
Where's the medicine?
你从哪儿弄来的？
Where did you get it?
我真的不知道
I really don't know.
我们正在找
We're looking for it.
他真的不知道
He really doesn't know.
我们也在找
We're looking for it, too.
东鼓
Dong-gu.
把他们都放进去，保证他们的安全
Put them all in and keep them safe.
好的，先生
All right, sir.
把 Kim Yang-ho 也带进来
Put Kim Yang-ho in, too.
过来
Come here.
就这一次
Just this once.
他们为什么要造游艇？
Why are they doing a yacht?
这些是什么？
What's all this?
为什么有这么多钥匙？
Why are there so many keys?
什么口信？
What's the message?
太多了
There are so many.
是游艇钥匙吗？
Is it a yacht key?
为什么只有这一张卡？
Why is this the only card?
这不是日本黑帮的作案模式吗？
Isn't this the Yakuza pattern?
露西？
Lucy?
露西
Lucy.
搜查这个地方
Search the place.
是的，长官
Yes, sir.
他把药藏在哪儿了？
Where did he hide the medicine?
仔细看
Look carefully.
这是什么？
What is it?
我不知道这是什么，但是锁得很紧
I don't know what this is, but it's locked tight.
我觉得这下面有东西
I think there's something down here.
是的
Yeah.
打开看看
Open it.
是的
Yes.
我觉得你应该这么做
I think you should do it.
这是什么？
Wow, what is this?
这是录音室里用过的一个按钮
It's a button that was used in the studio.
所以我才找不到
That's why I can't find it.
哇，太棒了
Wow, that's amazing.
我想我拍了一张成分组合的照片
I think I took a picture of the combination of the ingredients.
你来吧
You do it
就当是为了我
You do it for me
我可以用我的力量
I can use my strength
哦，天啊
Oh, man
嘿，这是个保险箱
Hey, this is a safe
你的力气怎么打得开？
How can you open it with your strength?
你得动动脑子
You have to use your brain
用我的大脑？
Use my brain?
我怎么能..
How can I...
没错
That's right.
我是说，你说里面是空的
I mean, you said it was empty.
哦，我的天啊
Oh, my God.
门没开
It's not open.
门开著
Oh, it's open.
It's open.
我弄坏了
I broke it.
这是什么？
What's this?
只有一个按钮
There's only a button.
跟我来
Follow me
什么？
What?
下面有什么？
What's down there?
为什么？
Why?
这是什么？
What's this?
有东西！
There's something!
葡萄！
Grapes!
我找到了
I found it
我找到里奇了
I found Ricky.
你确定吗？
Are you sure?
我肯定跟踪了你放出来的那个日本黑帮混蛋
I'm sure I followed the Yakuza bastard you released.
那孩子们呢？
What about the kids?
他们都在这里
They're all here.
我还带了一把没有注册的枪
I also brought a gun that wasn't registered.
准备好
Get ready.
是的
Yes.
因为这个
Because of this.
我们找到药了，现在怎么办？
We found the medicine. What do we do now?
Chorong 叫你去卖大白鲨，对吧？
Chorong told you to sell white shark, right?
是的
Yes.
去那里
Go there.
朱成哲会有反应的
Ju Sungcheol will react.
这连一万韩元都不到，对吧？
This is not even 10,000 won, right?
是的，没错
Yes, it is.
我们签合同吧
Let's sign the contract.
但是这辆车和图片上的不一样
But the car is different from the picture.
你不信吗？
You're not buying it?
我一直在给你看车，直到现在
I've been showing you the car until now.
开什么玩笑？
Are you kidding me?
这和照片有什么区别？
What's the difference with the picture?
算了，快点把合同拿来
Forget it. Hurry up and bring the contract.
是的，长官
Yes, sir.
佐荣晚上也很努力工作
Chorong works hard at night, too.
你在干什么? 你要卖车吗？
What are you doing? Are you selling the car?
- 这是什么?-还在那儿
What's this? It's still there.
是潜水车吗？
Is it a submerged car?
潜水车？
Submerged car?
是潜水车吗？
Is it a submerged car?
这是一辆潜水车
It's a submerged car.
这能行吗？
Can this work?
是的，这是一辆被水淹没的车
Yes, it's a submerged car.
是你开的，对吧？
You drove it, right?
是的，没错
Yes, that's right.
不是这辆车
It wasn't this car.
你让我买的
You told me to buy it.
你为什么要这么做？
Why did you do that?
没有，长官，我什么时候这么做了？
No, sir. When did I do that?
不久前
A while ago.
这个多少钱？
How much is this?
3000韩元
3,000 won.
3000韩元？
3,000 won?
3000韩元太便宜了
3,000 won is too cheap.
引擎没问题，你应该能拿到3000韩元
The engine is clean. You should get 3,000 won.
是的，先生
That's right, sir.
给我3000韩元
Give me 3,000 won.
什么，多少钱？
What? How much?
3000韩元
3,000 won.
3000韩元？
3,000 won?
是的，3000韩元
Yes, 3,000 won.
亲爱的，我能工作吗？
Honey, can I work?
我在废品站拿到了150韩元
I get 150 won at the scrapyard.
谢谢你
Thank you.
再见
Bye.
他不是我们要找的匪徒
He's not our gangster.
他是黑帮的
He's the gangster.
那个混蛋
That bastard.
请进
Come in.
是的，长官
Yes, sir.
你难道不好奇
Aren't you curious who worked on
死去的大白鲨？
the dead white shark?
你为什么要给我看？
Why are you showing me?
真烦人
It's annoying.
我很生气，别给我看
I'm getting angry. Don't show me.
真烦人
It's annoying.
我看得越多，就越生气
The more I see it, the more I get angry.
等等
Wait.
你为什么给我看这个？
Why are you showing me this?
你不想抓住罪犯吗？
Don't you want to catch the criminal?
是的
I do.
对吧？
Right?
是的
Yes.
但你能抓住他
But you can catch him.
我？
Me?
我们合作吧
Let's work together.
摆脱他，然后离开
Get rid of him and leave.
是的
Yes.
喂？
Hello?
你还记得我吗? 我是后街男孩的 Chorong
Do you remember me? I'm Chorong from the Backstreet Boys.
喂？
Hello?
什么？
What?
我只是碰巧手里有20公斤的超能力
I just happened to have a 20kg hyper in my hand.
这是给棒球运动员的，对吧？
This is for the baseball players, right?
喂？
Hello?
那又怎样？
So?
什么？
What?
我挂了
I hung up.
你是只狐貍
You're a fox.
把照片发给我
Send me the picture.
喂？
Hello?
情况怎么样？
What about the condition?
什么？
What?
好吧..
Well...
毒品交易
The drug deal...
我们做到了，对吧？
We did it, right?
我们再来一次
We'll do it again
即使我们卖了它
Even if we sell it
队长会收到的，因为这是谣言
the team leader will get it because it's a rumor
如果你交出毒品交易
If you hand over the drug deal
我们会还给你的
we'll return it to you
我把地址给你
I'll give you the address
一小时后你一个人来
You come alone after an hour
好吧
Okay
等一下
Wait a minute
毒品交易是你给我的吗？
Was it you who gave me the drug deal?
嘿
Hey
从现在开始，你要乖乖的
You have to be good from now on
是啊，你得好好表现
Yeah, you have to be good
你这个混蛋
You bastard
但他让我一个人来
But he told me to come alone
我一个人去吗？
Am I going alone?
你必须一个人去
You have to go alone
那我就不去了
Then I'm not going
泰秀
Tae Soo
我找到罪犯了
I found the criminal
我要当场抓住他
I'm going to catch him on the spot
你能跟他们一起走吗？
Can you move with the guys?
好的，我马上过去
Yeah, I'll be right there
你在哪里？
Where are you?
我把地址给你
I'll give you the address
你打算怎么办？
What are you going to do?
我要改变计划
I'm going to change my plan
你这个混蛋！
You're a bastard!
你想找到药，对吧？
You want to find the medicine, right?
你就是要杀他的人，对吧？
You're the one who's going to kill him, right?
你才是坏人
You're the bad guy.
我们做个交易吧
Let's make a deal.
我知道药在哪里
I know where the medicine is.
怎么会这样？
How did this happen?
你在想什么？
Hey, what are you thinking?
Chorong，你可以的
Chorong, Chorong, you can do it.
别紧张
Don't be nervous.
我真的要一个人去
I'm really going alone.
不用担心你
Don't worry about you.
把袋子送好
Just deliver the bag well.
我们要把它掩盖起来
We're going to cover it up.
如果朱成哲开枪呢？
What if Joo Sung-chul shoots a gun?
你必须避免
You have to avoid it.
上车
Get in.
妈的
Fuck.
操
Ah, f**k.
是的，我们到了
Yes, we're here.
到三楼来
Come up to the third floor.
是的
Yes.
我们准备一下
Let's get ready.
队长，是我 Cho Rung
Team leader, it's me, Cho Rung.
队长
Team leader.
我真他妈的生气！
I'm so fucking pissed off!
大哥！
Hyung-nim!
救救我！
Please save me!
你不是 Antoquin 吧？
You're not Antoquin, are you?
啊，这个朱成哲，那个狗娘养的
Ah, this Ju Sung-chul, that son of a bitch.
你个狗娘养的！
You son of a bitch!
他怎么还不出来，我好担心
Why isn't he coming out? I'm so anxious.
我们要进去吗？
Should we go in?
我觉得我们应该
I think we should.
打开看看
Open it.
是盐
It's salt.
我完蛋了
I'm fucked.
药呢？
Where's the medicine?
我不懂日语，请救救我
I don't know Japanese. Please save me.
药呢？
Where's the medicine?
警察知道了，我什么都不知道
The police know. I don't know anything.
狗娘养的！
Son of a bitch!
他为什么不接电话，发生什么事了吗？
Why isn't he answering his phone? Did something happen?
我们要上去吗？
Should we go up?
药在这里，对吧？
The medicine's here, right?
那个狗娘养的，那个狗娘养的，他在耍我
That son of a bitch, that son of a bitch, he's messing with me.
瑞琪，这地方很危险，我们换个地方吧
Riki, this place is dangerous. Let's move to another place.
我能马上看看吗？
Can I see it right away?
带上他
Bring him.
是的
Yes.
来吧！
Come on!
你们这些混蛋！
You bastards!
抓住他！
Catch him!
你没事吧？
Are you okay?
我没事
I'm fine.
快点
Hurry up.
东鼓！
Dong-gu!
嘿！
Hey!
你! 你是什么东西！
You! What are you!
你在干什么，我在问你！
What are you, I'm asking you!
你这个混蛋！
You bastard!
嘿，跟教授说说这个
Hey, tell the professor about this.
是的，长官
Yes, sir.
嘿！
Hey!
药呢？
Where's the medicine?
在哪里？
Where is it?
在抽屉里
It's in the drawer.
给我！
Give it to me!
对不起
I'm sorry.
嘿 Choo Sun-cheol
Hey, Choo Sun-cheol.
开什么玩笑？
Are you kidding me?
你现在在哪，混蛋？
Where are you right now, you bastard?
我要吃药
I'll take the medicine.
你是个暗箭伤人的人
You're a backstabber.
Choo Sun-cheol 停下了火车
Choo Sun-cheol stopped the train.
滚出去
Get out of here.
太疼了，别打我了
It hurts so much. Stop hitting me.
喂，朱松哲那个王八蛋呢？
Hey, where is that bastard Ju Sung-chul?
该死，我没时间了
Damn it. I don't have time.
马哈
Maha.
獒树
Osu.
马哈，你也是马西人吗？
Maha, are you a Masi too?
呃..
Ugh...
拿著这个！
Take this!
干得好
Good job.
这太难了
This is hard.
你无处可逃了
There's nowhere to run.
我要杀了你
I'll kill you.
嘿，那把刀
Hey, that knife.
等一下
Wait a minute.
把证据放在这里
Put the evidence in here.
闭嘴！
Shut up!
我告诉过你，你这个混蛋
I told you, you bastard.
呃..
Ugh...
该死
Damn it.
Seok-joo! Seok-joo！
Seok-joo! Seok-joo!
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
米奇呢，你抓到他了吗？
What about Mickey? Did you catch him?
你抓到他了吗？
Did you catch him?
你做到了！
You did!
嘿，这些人都在车里
Hey, these guys are all in the car.
晚点回来
Come back late.
因为你在找他，所以监控摄像头都坏了
The security cameras are all dead because you're looking for him.
我们得在他逃跑之前抓住他
Hey, we have to catch this guy before he runs away.
请帮我拿一下
Please hold this for a second.
这是什么？
What is it?
你没事吧？
Are you okay?
嘿，等一下
Hey, wait a minute.
这个？
This?
你们在这里做什么？
What are you guys doing here?
搞定它
Take care of it.
那是我们的退休金
That's our retirement money.
检查你的护照
Check your passport.
飞船准备好了吗？
Is the ship ready?
是的
Yes.
我们只需要去南非然后离开
We just have to go to South Africa and leave.
我觉得时机正好
I think the timing is good.
船长要我们明早过去
The captain wants us to come up tomorrow morning.
如果你想见我，告诉他来中国
If you want to meet me, tell him to come to China.
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
嘿! 你这个混蛋！
Hey! You bastard!
你没死？
You're not dead?
当当！
Ta-da!
嘿，下来挡住他！
Hey, come down and block him!
你这个混蛋！
You bastard!
别过来！
Don't come!
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
放开我！
Let me go!
等等！
Wait!
我必须抓住他！
I have to catch him!
对不起
I'm sorry.
我是光洙家的人
I'm a Gwang-soo.
我也是警察！
I'm a police too!
你找到他了吗？
Did you track him down?
他在逃跑吗？
Is he running away?
谁在逃跑？
Who's running away?
他在等你
He's waiting for you.
快来
Come quickly.
你觉得警察能杀人吗？
You think a cop can kill a man?
如果你努力工作，你可以杀死一个人
You can kill a man if you work hard.
你不能按法律说的做
You can't do what the law says.
你应该挨打
You should get beaten up.
啊！
Ugh!
你肋骨断了吗？
Did your ribs break?
噢！
Ow!
我全身都疼
My whole body hurts.
嘿 Masukdo
Hey, Masukdo.
我们做个交易吧
Let's make a deal.
大概有3000亿
It's about 300 billion.
如果我们平分
If we split it...
嘿，嘿，嘿
Hey, hey, hey.
别提五点到五点
Don't even talk about 5 to 5.
反正我也要去
I'm coming anyway.
那你今天就死定了
Then you're going to die today.
你可以做 Mukbi
You can do the Mukbi.
我给你介绍个律师
I'll introduce you to a lawyer.
进来吧
Come on in.
打个招呼，我叫阿珠
Say hello. I'm Ju.
你个狗娘养的！
You son of a bitch!
你说完了吗？
Are you done?
嘿！
Hey!
Seok-do，发生什么事了？
Seok-do, what happened?
请把这里收拾干净
Please clean up the mess.
珠星，你没事吧？
Hey, Joo-sung, are you okay?
我觉得自己老了
I feel old.
嘿，嘿，嘿，你不能误会他
Hey, hey, hey, you can't get him wrong.
叫救护车
Call the ambulance.
日本黑帮组织已经被逮捕，该组织将新药 Hyper 带到韩国并在全国各地销售
The Japanese yakuza organization that brought the new drug, Hyper, to Korea and distributed it all over the country, has been arrested.
与此同时，把钱带给黑帮的人现在被证明是个侦探，这太令人震惊了
Meanwhile, the person who brought the money to the yakuza is now proven to be a detective, which is shocking.
干得好
Good job.
天经常下雨，但是我们的侦探很酷，很棒
It rained a lot, but our detective was very cool and good.
干得好
Good job.
干得好，干得好
Good job, good job.
没错，我被撞晕过去了
That's right. I got hit and passed out.
嘿，嘿，你没有面包我就放心了
Hey, hey, it's a relief that you don't have bread.
那就在这里等一下
Then wait a minute here.
这是什么？
What's this?
意外收获！
Bonus!
我的呢？
Where's mine?
你付我一百万韩元
You pay me a million won.
你把它弄坏了
You broke it like that.
是啊
Oh, well, yeah.
我明天一大早有个会议，所以我要先起床
I have a meeting early tomorrow morning, so I'll get up first.
不，不
No, no.
干得好，警探们
Good job, detectives.
干得好
Good job.
嘿，嘿，嘿
Hey, hey, hey.
我会付钱的
I'll pay.
请给我一份菜单
Please give me a menu.
给我一份菜单
Give me a menu.
让我们一起举杯
Let's have a toast as a whole.
广苏大学，国防部，你们都做得很好
Gwangsu University, the Ministry of National Defense, all of you did a great job.
大家一起
Let's all
干杯！
Cheers!
谢谢你的礼物
Thank you for the gift.
昨天的事我很抱歉
I'm sorry about yesterday.
是不是太贵了? 你没事吧？
Isn't it too expensive? Are you okay?
别担心
Don't worry.
走，走
Go, go.
主席，你在吗？
Chairman, are you here?
你碰过所有的新产品吗？
Did you touch all the new products?
别担心，我都摸过了
Don't worry. I've touched it all.
我看看
Let's see.
这边走
Come this way.
把积分降到7000分
Hey, put this down to 7,000 points.
人们就是这样偷口袋的
That's how people lift their pockets.
因为受伤的骄傲
Because of the hurt pride.
那不是我的车吗？
Isn't that my car?
那个混蛋怎么了？
What's with that bastard?
哪个混蛋动了我的车？
What bastard is touching my car?
你是谁？
Who are you?
嘿，Jang Hee-soo. 你必须和我合作
Hey, Jang Hee-soo. You have to work with me.
你突然出现，真烦人
You're suddenly here. You're so annoying.